fantasyfootballstarters.com 2014-11-08

# Privacy Policy for www.fantasyfootballstarters.com

Effective on July 16, 2010 

This privacy statement describes how Fantasy Football Starters collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: [www.fantasyfootballstarters.com ](https://www.fantasyfootballstarters.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

**TRUSTe**

Fantasy Football Starters is a Participant in the TRUSTe Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to advance privacy and trust in the networked world. This Web site has agreed to have its privacy practices monitored for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact us at [info@fantasyfootballstarters.com ](mailto:info@fantasyfootballstarters.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
  * Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [info@fantasyfootballstarters.com ](mailto:info@fantasyfootballstarters.com).

## Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, 
  * if Fantasy Football Starters is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.

_Web beacons_

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

Our Web pages may also contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that are set by our third party partners. Web beacons are used along with cookies enabling our partners to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.

We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

_Links to Other Web Sites_

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Fantasy Football Starters. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [info@fantasyfootballstarters.com](mailto:info@fantasyfootballstarters.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [info@fantasyfootballstarters.com ](mailto:info@fantasyfootballstarters.com)

## Additional Policy Information

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at [info@fantasyfootballstarters.com ](mailto:info@fantasyfootballstarters.com).

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

Fantasy Football Starters 

PO Box 25732 

Scottsdale, AZ, United States 85255
